{
    "question": "Contoh percakapan expression care",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "how poor you are<br>what a pity<br>i am sorry to hear that",
            "attachments": []
        },
        {
            "answer": "Situation : Your friend is sad.<br><br>Ana : <strong>Are you okay? You look so sad.</strong><br>Nia : <em>No, I&#039;m not okay.</em> I feel so sad because I had a fight with my brother yesterday.<br>Ana : Why?<br>Nia : He took my favorite novel without asking my permission and he ripped it! How can I not sad? He even not sorry at all and when I yelled at him, he yelled me back with his ridiculous reason that why should I got sad over a novel!<br>Ana : You must be really hurt...<br>Nia : Of couse I do.<br>Ana : <strong>What should I do to cheer you up?</strong><br>Nia : <em>Thanks for your attention</em> but no, sorry.<br>Ana : <strong>Really?</strong> I&#039;m sorry I can&#039;t help you much.<br>Nia: <em>Yeah, thanks</em>.<br><br><strong>bold: expressions<br></strong><em>italic: responses</em><strong><br></strong>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "buatin-sinopsis-film-cloudy-a-chance-of-meatballs-2-dong-pake-bhs-151",
            "question": "buatin sinopsis film cloudy a chance of meatballs 2 dong pake bhs indonesia gpp..nanti aku yang translate sendiri...tolong bantu ya",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "It&#039;s always been Flint&#039;s dream \nto be recognized as a great inventor, but everything changes when he \ndiscovers that his most infamous machine (which turns water into food) \nis still operating and is now creating food-animal hybrids - \n\"foodimals!\" With the fate of humanity in his hands, Chester sends Flint\n and his friends on a dangerously delicious mission - to battle hungry \ntacodiles, shrimpanzees, hippotatomuses, cheespiders and other food \ncreatures to save the world again!            \n                <span>- <span>Written by\nColumbia Pictures</span></span>        \n            <span>\nFlint Lockwood is a genius who created a machine that turns water into \nfood which went out of control. Flint would stop it. He would set out to\n build his own lab with Sam Sparks. But Chester V, the scientist who \ninspired Flint comes to the island to clean up the mess, the machine \nmade, and offers Flint a job at his lab. Flint takes it. Later, Dr. V \ntells him that the machine is now creating living food\n and they could be a threat. So he goes back to the island along with \nhis friends including Sam to stop it. But Sam tells flint that they \ncould acting hastily but Dr. V convinces Flint otherwise. So they leave \nFlint and eventually learn the truth.            </span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bantu-nyusun-kata-kata-ne-jadi-klimat-yg-bner-ya-yang-dimulai-dri-452",
            "question": "Bantu nyusun kata-kata ne jadi klimat yg bner ya yang dimulai dri yg bergaris bawah sama bantu buatkan CONDITIONAL SENTENCE TIPE 2    arrange the jumbled words to form meaningful sentences,starting with the underlined words.\r\n1. phone-puppet-his-invite-the-I-number-my-see-Finto-know-will-if-show-to-I-at-place\r\n2. and-holiday-Bali-if-have-will-his-Lombok-long-go-year-Mr. Kukuh-family-to-they-and-this-a\u00a0mohon di bantu",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. If\u00a0 I know his phone number, I will invite Finto to the puppet show at my place.<br>2. If Mr. Kukuh and his family go to Bali, they will have a long holiday to Lombok this year.<br>Sorry kalau salah, baru pemula hehehe<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bisa-gak-buatin-pidato-dari-teks-ini-plastic-surgery-is-not-s-r-624",
            "question": "Bisa gak buatin pidato dari teks ini\u00a0    plastic surgery is not s recent phenimenon, but it was appeared since 3000 years ago. in the past, it was for medical purpose but now it is creating beuty and trend to modify some part of body.\r\nmany people nowaday want to be extraordinary such as animal or less human by plastic surgery. they modifying their faces and bodies to make them more animal like. meny so called 'lizard people' have had their tongues split. a woman who changed her face like a cat. other people gone beyond different kinds of tattoos.\r\nthe people who done outcast actually they lack self respect and have adesperate need for attention. they should be treated by psychiatrist, not plastic surgeons. and we should be aware of society that no longer wants to look human",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "hi people, today i will tell you about plastic surgery. plastic surgery appeared 3000 years ago, in the past, it was for medical purpose but now it is only for a change of appearance. many people nowdays want to have a beautiful or handsome face, in other words &#039;being closer to perfections in the matter of appearance&#039;. but some people have some really weird tastes and they tried to be less human-like, by using plastic surgery, they tried to looks like a lizard or cats, and many other animals. the people that took plastic surgery is usually people who is not satisfied with their looks, or their body. they degraded\u00a0the gods creation, and try to be more &#039;perfect&#039;, however they sometime did not look at the risk. you see, if the surgery failed, then can you even imagine what your body or face would look like? and because of that i highly recommend not to take plastic surgery, and appreciate what god has given to us.\u00a0\u00a0<br><br>^aku tambahin beberapa informasi\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "terdiri-dari-apa-sajakah-causative-have-itu-798",
            "question": "Terdiri dari apa sajakah causative have itu",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Causative verb menunjukkan bahwa seseorang/sesuatu secara tidak langsung bertanggung jawab terhadap sebuah tindakan. Subjek tidak melakukan tindakan itu sendiri, tetapi justru menyebabkan seseorang/sesuatu yang lain melakukannya. Contoh:<br>- Yesterday I had my hair cut.<br>Pembicara pada kalimat diatas tidak memotong sendiri rambutnya, tetapi justru membuat orang lain melakukannya \u2013 Saya \u201cmenyebabkan\u201d mereka memotong rambut saya.<br>Have<br>Have merupakan causative verb yang umum. Ketimbang melakukan sesuatu dengan diri kita sendiri, kita \u201cmenyuruh\u201d orang yang lain untuk melakukannya. Bentuknya sebagai berikut:<br>Kata kerja \u201cto have\u201d + objek + past participle (verb 3). Contoh:<br>- I had my jacket cleaned yesterday.<br>- Did you have your computer fixed?<br>Terkadang kita menggunakan have sebagai causative verb ketika kita ingin melakukan tindakan oleh diri kita sendiri. Contoh:<br>- When will the report be ready? I\u2019ll do it by tomorrow morning. &gt;&gt;<br>- When will the report be ready? I\u2019ll have it done by tomorrow morning.<br>Dengan menggunakan causative, kalimat ke-dua diatas mengalihkan perhatian dari pelaku tindakan, dan lebih memberikan perhatian kepada tindakan yang sedang dilakukan. Ini kedengaran sopan dan profesional.<br>Get<br>Get sering digunakan ketimbang have. Contoh:<br>\u2022\tI got my computer fixed \u2013 I had my computer fixed. Kedua kalimat ini maknanya sama.<br>\u2022\tI got my jacket cleaned. \u2013 I had my jacket cleaned. Kedua kalimat ini maknanya sama.<br>Causative verbs sering digunakan bersama dengan pengalaman-pengalaman negatif. Pada situasi-situasi ini lebih umum menggunakan have. Contoh:<br>\u2022\tI had my wallet stolen. (Saya sebenarnya tidak menyebabkan dompet saya dicuri \u2013 seseorang mencuri dompet saya dariku)<br><span>\u2022\tShe had her window smashed.<br><br></span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-percakapan-making-and-handling-cancellation-gimana-ya-ada-918",
            "question": "Contoh percakapan making and handling cancellation gimana ya?\r\nada yang bisa bantu",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "David : Excuse me. I think there is a mistake in our bill. We didn&#039;t have dinner here lst night.<br>Receptionist : I&#039;m sorry, sir. Here&#039;s the bill from the hotel restaurant. It&#039;s got your signature on it.<br>David : But that&#039;s not my signature. I&#039;d like to speak to the manager.<br>Receptionist : I&#039;m sorry, sir. The manager is busy.<br>Manager : You have a complaint about your bill, sir ?<br>David : Yes. I&#039;m afraid there&#039;s a mistake. We didn&#039;t have dinner in the restaurant last night.<br>Manager : But this looks like your signature on the restaurant bill.<br>Let me see. Oh dear I&#039;m very sorry. There&#039;s another couple called Morris in the hotel.<br>They had dinner last night. Not you. I do apologize.<br><br>sudah ya cukup :)\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-soal-expression-of-suggestioun-478",
            "question": "Contoh soal expression of suggestioun? \u00a0",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "woman ; l think the weather is not friendly enough for us to do outdoor activites.<br>mam ; <br>narator ; what will the mam likely reply with?<br>a. enjoy your flight<br>b.let&#039;s go to the beach.<br>c. yes . we&#039;d better cancel our trip<br>d. l don&#039;t think l can attend the meeting<br><br>jawaban c<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-buat-expressing-annoyance-2-orang-yang-berada-dalam-kelas-110",
            "question": "Tolong buat expressing annoyance 2 orang yang berada dalam kelas, jumlah percakapan 1 orang 5 percakapan    please help me :)\u00a0",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "A: i&#039;m so tired.<br>B: me too. it&#039;s boring here<br>C: and the whether feels so timid. i don&#039;t like it<br>D: me neither.<br>E: hey hey why don&#039;t we play soccer instead?<br>A: no thank you. i think it will cost much effort either<br><br>maaf gabisa buat yang bagus, isi umpatan gitu katanya",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "aku-dapt-tugas-dari-guru-binggris-ku-disusruh-membuat-cerita-sp-750",
            "question": "aku dapt tugas dari guru b.inggris ku disusruh membuat cerita \"spoof\" dari pngalaman pribadi, tapi aku bingung gimana crtanya. tlg bantu ya",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "kamu pasti punya kan pengalaman lucu ,,, kamu tulis aja bhs indonesianya nntik saya coba nerjemahin<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buatlah-contoh-pecakapan-bahasa-inggris-tentang-pemesanan-meja-di-618",
            "question": "Buatlah contoh pecakapan bahasa inggris tentang pemesanan meja di restoran..",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "A: i want to ask permission<br>B: yes of course<br>A: two days there will be an event in my home, can i order 2 pieces of table<br>B: of course may be happy<br>A: ok i&#039;ll wait for tomorrow<br>B: okay, thank you&#039;ve booked a table here<br>A: you&#039;re welcome<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<span>A: Good afternoon <br>b: Good afternoon, can I help you? <br>A: I would like to reserve a table, for tomorrow afternoon? <br>b: yes, it could. for how many people? <br>A: I would like to reserve a table for lunch two people! <br>B: Yes sir, tomorrow daytime table number five <br>A: Thank you<span>.</span></span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "kalimat-bahasa-inggris-noun-clause-387",
            "question": "Kalimat bahasa inggris\u00a0noun clause",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "I forgot that the fact was very important<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "mungkin yang first conditional,second conditional,sama third conditional<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}